lifequiz.me 2019-03-31

# Privacy - Lifequiz

All content you see here is purely for entertainment purpose.

**What information do we collect?**

We MAY collect the following data from your profile:

  * Your Firstname and Lastname
  * Your Gender
  * Your Photo
  * Your Email Address
  * Your Friends list

Google, as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * Storing records temporarily 
  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To send periodic emails

**○ We respect your privacy and do not tolerate spam and will never share, sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party. Nor will we send you unsolicited email.**

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Cookies, What are Cookies?**

  1. Cookies are small data files downloaded and stored on user’s device while browsing a website, often used to keep record of actions taken on such website or track related browsing activity.
  2. For additional information regarding Cookies and the way to control them, please check out the Help file of your browser or visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers’ hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

**We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and user behavior.**

  1. We may use Cookies in order to ensure proper operation, collect Non-Personal Information, verify information, tailor the Website to your specific preferences and ensure information security. In addition, certain services (such as the Google Services and the Facebook Services) require the use of cookies. Additionally, we may use third-party content companies in order to present content through the Website. Such parties may use Cookies placed on your device (as well as web beacons and other similar technologies) in order to adjust or track the content presented through the Website.
  2. Certain third parties providing the content to our Website (such as quizzes, puzzles etc.) may also use cookies, web-beacons and other similar tools in order to collect Non-Personal Information, for marketing and advertising purposes.
  3. Regarding use of Cookies by third-party content companies, please note that such use is subject to the privacy policy of said parties and is not subject to this Privacy Policy (for example, regarding advertisements served by Google, see <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads>).

**Third party links**

Occasionally at our discretion we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent which is given by using our site.   
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their Account Page and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

**Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 14 years old or older. If you are 13 and under please DO NOT use our site.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.lifequiz.me/terms.php) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.  
Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent fully to our privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**

Please contact us at admin@lifequiz.me for any question concerting your privacy or any violation thereof. Please also use the above contact information details if you wish to opt-out of certain services and offers described under this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change our Privacy Policy at anytime without prior notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post those changes on this page.

**○ I hereby approve that I have read and acknowledged the terms of this Privacy Policy and further allow you to send me promotional emails and to collect and use my personal and non-personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.**

This document was last updated on July 01, 2018
